<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<schemalist>
    <schema path="/re/jcm/xmbos/xmbshell/" id="re.jcm.xmbos.xmbshell">
        <key name='font-path' type='s'>
            <default>'/usr/share/fonts/truetype/ubuntu/Ubuntu-R.ttf'</default>
            <summary>Font</summary>
            <description>
                Path to the font to use to render text.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='wave-color' type='s'>
            <default>'#f9f9f9'</default>
            <summary>Wave color</summary>
            <description>
                Color of the background wave.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='date-time-format' type='s'>
            <default>'m/%d %H:%M'</default>
            <summary>Date Time format</summary>
            <description>
                Format to use to display the date and time.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='date-time-x-offset' type='d'>
            <default>0.0</default>
            <summary>Date Time x offset</summary>
            <description>
                Offset (in relative screen units) to move the date time by.
                This is useful when setting a longer format for the date time.
            </description>
        </key>
    </schema>
    <schema path="/re/jcm/xmbos/xmbshell/render/" id="re.jcm.xmbos.xmbshell.render">
        <key name='vsync' type='b'>
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Render with VSync</summary>
            <description>
                When enabled, the shell will render with VSync, which avoids screen tearing,
                but limits the FPS to the refresh rate of the monitor.
                This can cause input lag and can therefore be disabled to let the shell render as fast as possible.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='max-fps' type='i'>
            <default>200</default>
            <summary>Maximum FPS</summary>
            <description>
                Limits the maximum FPS the shell can render.
                This can be useful to avoid the shell rendering as fast as possible and using all the resources.
                When set to 0 (or a negative value), the shell will render as fast as possible.
                When VSync is enabled this setting is ignored if it is higher than the refresh rate of the monitor.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='sample-count' type='i'>
            <default>4</default>
            <summary>Sample count</summary>
            <description>
                The number of samples to use for multisampling.
                This can be useful to improve the quality of the rendering, but it can also be more resource intensive.
                A value of 1 disables multisampling.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='show-fps' type='b'>
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Show FPS</summary>
            <description>
                When enabled, the shell will show the FPS in the top left corner of the screen.
            </description>
        </key>
        <key name='show-mem' type='b'>
            <default>true</default>
            <summary>Show memory usage</summary>
            <description>
                When enabled, the shell will show the memory usage in the top right corner of the screen.
            </description>
        </key>
    </schema>
</schemalist>
